<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Loreshelf - notes organizer</title>
    <link>https://loreshelf.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Loreshelf - notes organizer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loreshelf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://loreshelf.com/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loreshelf.com/community/</guid>
      <description>Community      Topics  Staying informed   Code contribution   Issue reporting        Staying informed   Follow and join us on Loreshelf Subreddit.   Code contribution   Loreshelf is an Open Source project licensed under the GNU General Public License v3. The source code is hosted on GitHub.   Issue reporting   Look up and report found Loreshelf issues on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://loreshelf.com/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loreshelf.com/license/</guid>
      <description>License  Updated 8/31/2020     Loreshelf is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; version 3 of the License. Loreshelf is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s new</title>
      <link>https://loreshelf.com/whats-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loreshelf.com/whats-new/</guid>
      <description>What&#39;s new  Find out what&#39;s new in the latest Loreshelf release.     Changelog v1.0 - September 3th, 2020 This is the initial release of Loreshelf.
   New Feature    Slash Commands  Add new content with slash commands. For example headers, tables, icons, quotes, and more.       New Feature    Mentions  Mention and link to the related information across notebooks and workspaces.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>